The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
I'm not sure how strong the Fire Demon Country is.
I have 100 years
to find powerful spells and artifacts to beat it.
Large Forest
Fire Demon Country
For example...
Ling Tianhou's sword energy.
Unfortunately, I was drunk on the Celestial Ascension Fruits back then.
Maybe Zi Shu's sword energy
is still hidden in his body.
Tong Yun
He Yun Sect disciple
Middle stage Soul Transformation
This is a good treasure !
It can instantly kill even a Soul Transformation.
Since I found it,
I must get it.
Who !?
Where did this old monster come from ?
It would be a real shame
to give it up just like this...
Please allow me to take my Junior Brother's body back.
Your Junior Brother ?
I am Tong Yun
and he is my junior brother Zhou Qu.
Look,
the golden glow of this sword energy
is precisely the Purple Sky Sword Technique of our He Yun Sect.
This...
this is sword energy capable of fighting Ascendant cultivators !
So...
he was your Junior Brother, right ?
Exactly !
Give him a proper burial.
Thank you Senior for your kindness,
Junior will now take his...
I will bury my Junior Brother !
Damned sword energy !
I almost died for it !
Demon Emperor's camp
Border of the Fire Demon Country
The Fire Demon Country's luck
is about to turn.
Who dares to intrude !?
Halt !
Brother Wang,
long time no see.
Wang Lin
greets the Demon Emperor.
You don't need to be formal with me.
After all, you're the Envoy chosen by the Ancestral Spirit.
Your status is the same as mine.
From now on,
you can just call me Gu Yundun.
I thought my disguise was flawless
back when we drank together on the boat.
But looking at it now,
you had probably guessed my identity long ago.
You have a majestic aura.
What difference does it make
when you try to hide it ?
Brother Wang's visit today
isn't just for reminiscing, is it ?
If I recall correctly,
Mo Fei's helper
was also one of the 12 Sword of the Da Lou Sword Sect.
Where is Mo Fei ?
Mo Fei is already a Vice Commander-in-Chief.
He should currently be with the Tian Commander in Chief.
Together, they are leading the left army.
Their camp is outside the Fire Demon Country's Songtao City.
This is the Sky Demon Jade Slip,
whoever holds this jade slip
is my voice.
If anyone disrespects you,
you can order the Tian Commander-in-Chief to kill them.
Thank you.
Your Majesty just gave him the jade like that ?
Focusing only on the present
will cost you the future.
Since the Ancestral Spirit values Wang Lin so highly,
then he must have a plan in mind.
Battlefield of Songtao City
Fire Demon Country
Wang Lin,
disrupting a military formation without authorization
is a grave offense !
Do you have a death wish ?
He must be here to get his revenge for my assassination attempt back then...
By the Emperor's order,
capture and execute Mo Fei.
Even if it's the Demon Emperor's order,
I can't surrender without a fight !
Since Mo Fei is being discarded,
I shouldn't get entangled in this battle.
You...
Why ?
I want your sword energy.
Underworld Finger !
I'm not in a hurry
to take your life.
Cave Dwelling
Sky Demon Country
Wang Lin,
if you dare to kill me
The Da Lou Sword Sect will hunt you down !
Then that saves me the trouble of looking for them.
I couldn't ask for more.
Soul Search !
One month ago,
all the 12 Swords were summoned to the Fire Demon Country.
The one who summoned them
is named Greed.
Greed...
According to his memory,
Greed's cultivation has reached Illusory Yin.
Compared to Situ Nan's Corporeal Yang,
he is only one step behind.
Situ Nan...
Situ once told me
that he was gravely injured by 3 people back then.
He is one of the cultivators who attacked Situ Nan.
He knows about the Heaven Defying Bead.
This person
must be a formidable foe.
If Greed gathered everyone,
then what did he discover ?
What's hidden within the Fire Demon Country
that could attract someone above Ascendant ?
And he's acting so secretively...
The Blood Ancestor...
Greed...
Demon Spirit Land
Fire Demon Country
Sky Demon Country
Dragon Pool
Metal Demon Country
Thunder Demon Country
Wind Demon Country
Water Demon Country
Wood Demon Country
Spirit Demon Country
Cloud Demon Country
Demon Spirit Land...
Could it be that this place is the cultivation cave of a Celestial
before the Celestial Realm even shattered !?
The Blood Ancestor asked you to enter the Demon Spirit Land.
What is he plotting exactly ?
You can try to guess, Wang Lin.
Even if you rack your brains,
you will never learn even half of the truth !
Even if you don't say a word,
I'll deduce the truth sooner or later anyway.
If you tell me voluntarily,
I will set you free
when I leave the Demon Spirit Land.
The Demon Spirit Land
is the cultivation cave of an Ancient Celestial.
Am I right ?
Father repeatedly told me to keep the secret...
But...
he already guessed this much
with just a few scattered clues.
If I want to regain my freedom,
this might be
my last chance.
I can tell you !
But you must swear on your Dao Heart
to keep your promise !
Since I have promised you,
I will not go back on my word.
But you are not qualified
to make me swear on my Dao Heart.
The whole Demon Spirit Land
is the cave world of Celestial Emperor Qing Lin.
I am Qing Lin.
Qing Lin was the number one powerhouse of the Celestial Realm.
It is said that when the Celestial Realm collapsed,
Qing Lin defended it all alone,
only to vanish after being severely injured
leaving only his cave behind.
It is said
that whoever inherits his cave
may have a glimpse at what the 3rd step of the Dao is.
No wonder they're all flocking here.
Then what was the place
you brought me to ?
Back then,
my father came in here with a group of old monsters
but they weren't strong enough.
The first 3 fake caves
fell in the hands of Ling Tianhou,
the All-Seer,
and the Cloud Celestial Couple.
But no one knew
that Qing Lin's cave world
has 4 fake caves and a single real cave.
The place we went to
is the fourth fake cave.
You were eager to claim the fake cave
to set up a scheme for the Blood Ancestor, right ?
In 10 years, my father the Blood Ancestor,
your master the All-Seer,
Ling Tianhou, and other powerhouses will come in.
The fake caves are the gates
and the golden token is the key.
Claim all 4 fake caves
and the real cave will appear.
The Blood Ancestor sure is cunning.
He's the only one that knows the existence of the fourth cave.
He withholds information from the others to take the initiative.
But the All-Seer personally designated me to enter the Demon Spirit Land...
For what purpose ?
The war between Sky Demon and Fire Demon countries
is a great opportunity for our tribe to grow !
In this expedition,
we must spread the fame of our Soul Refining Tribe !
We will live up to your expectations !
Ancestor !
We pay respect to the Ancestor.
Why have you gathered here ?
Ancestor,
we wish to go to participate in the current war
to collect souls for you
and to strengthen our tribe.
The battlefield is too far
and the journey is full of dangers.
Formation, activate !
Transfer !
This is the border of the Sky Demon Country
and also...
the new location of our Soul Refining Tribe.
The Ancestor is building us a new Soul Refining Tribe !
The Ancestor's power is limitless !
Amazing !
As expected of the Ancestor !
New Soul Refining Tribe
These are strands of slaughter energy.
The more you kill, the more it multiplies.
It can also protect you in times of crisis
to ensure your safety.
Thank you, Ancestor !
Now, I will cultivate in seclusion.
Do not disturb me
unless it's necessary.
Understood !
Fire Demon Country
Sky Demon City
Soul Refining Tribe
Battlefield
Fire Demon Country
The Scattered Devil is hard to tame.
I can only use my Origin Soul to deepen the imprint.
Soul Refining Sect
Fire Demon Country
Sky Demon Country
Soul Refining Sect
Watch the prisoners carefully !
Slow down,
come over here !
Back then, my cultivation was only Soul Transformation
and I was barely able to open the first seal.
Now that I'm Ascendant,
It's time to remove the second seal.
This lightning's power is extraordinary !
If I undo the second seal,
I won't be able to control it with the Beast Trap.
I'll have to subdue it with my own strength.
Second seal...
open !
Damn beast,
submit to me !
10 years later
Fire Demon Country
Sky Demon Country
We have guests.
This time, the Celestial Ancestor ordered us
to capture this Wang Lin !
Jin Shaofei
Cultivation Union member
Middle stage Soul Transformation
The Celestial Ancestor even sent a Celestial Guardian.
We are sure to succeed this time.
I wonder if this Wang Lin of the Soul Refining Tribe
and the Wang Lin of the Heavenly Fate Sect
are the same person...
Sun Yunshan,
what are you thinking ?
Master,
I...
If it weren't for your sister's sake,
do you think you would have been included
in an opportunity to earn merit
like capturing this Wang Lin ?
Break the formation !
For the Celestial Ancestor !
You, go.
The Ancestor invites you in.
He's got some sense,
let's go !
Such a massive tribe...
Ancestor,
the guests have arrived.
Esteemed guests from afar,
what brings you here ?
It's really him !
You have some talent.
Kneel, and by the Celestial Ancestor's decree,
you'll be part of the union.
The Cultivation Union ?
Is it worthy of me ?
You dare to insult our Celestial Ancestor !
Celestial Guardian,
crush this ant !
It's over...
Celestial Guardian
Cultivation Union member
Early stage Ascendant
Blasphemers of the Celestial
must be utterly annihilated !
Fall.
Good ! Good !
With strength like yours,
you are worthy of being enlightened by the Celestial Ancestor !
Join our union !
Brother Wang, don't !
That Cultivation Union
is a trap !
Sun Yunshan,
you dare betray the Celestial Ancestor !?
Noisy.
Brother Sun,
you can speak.
It's all my fault...
I'm the one that let my sister
join that Cultivation Union.
That's why we ended up like this.
I beg Brother Wang,
please save my Xuan Yuan Sect !
The Celestial Ancestor
plants Celestial Seeds in people's bodies.
These Celestial Seeds can seize one's mind
to make people work for him !
Celestials Seeds ?
The Celestial Ancestor's origins are unclear.
He claims to be a Celestial of the Celestial Realm.
Not only does he control us with the Celestial Seeds
but his subordinates
also include 9 powerful Celestial Guardians !
The celestial spiritual energy within this Celestial Crystal is immense...
It's a pity there's a Divine Sense around it
that makes this celestial spiritual energy unusable.
Celestial Seeds...
Celestial Crystals...
Brother Sun,
do you know where I can find
that Cultivation Union ?
The Cultivation Union and the Cultivation Alliance have nothing to do with eachother. The beast of the God Slaying Chariot is called a Silver Horn Thunder Beast.
---
The lightning descended from the sky and landed on the spirit beast’s body. The successive lightning bolts linked together, forming a line.
The spirit beast’s body was surrounded in a sphere of lightning. It was standing, but it gradually lied down and soon it turned into a qilin-like beast.
However, it wasn’t a qilin, but a beast even more rare than qilin in the Celestial Realm, a thunder beast! A silver horn slowly drilled out from its head under the effects of the lightning.
Wang Lin’s eyes revealed a hint of disappointment when he saw the silver horn. He let out a sigh and then moved forward. As his hand drew in the air, the fourth blood symbol was complete. He grabbed the blood symbol and headed straight for the thunder beast.
“According to the jade, if the second seal on the second war chariot is activated perfectly, a golden horn should appear…” He immediately closed in on the thunder beast, charged directly through the lightning, and directly pressed the blood symbol between the spirit beast’s eyebrows.
The timing he picked was the one the jade mentioned. The moment that the spirit beast evolves into a thunder beast was the only moment for imprinting in its life. This moment was specifically left behind by the maker to place an imprint on the beast.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.